<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>meteor on Line Ton That</title>
    <link>https://linetonthat.github.io/tags/meteor/</link>
    <description>Recent content in meteor on Line Ton That</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 21:33:52 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://linetonthat.github.io/tags/meteor/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Adapting from A2 to A4 format: Can you spot the differences?</title>
      <link>https://linetonthat.github.io/post/going-from-a2-to-a4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 21:33:52 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://linetonthat.github.io/post/going-from-a2-to-a4/</guid>
      <description>Prior to their annual event, the International Meteor Organization asked its members if they had a poster to share. Although I was unable to attend the event, I submitted a poster in the form of a visual meteor shower calendar for 2023. The organization responded that they could include this poster in their quarterly journal on the back cover. Since their print size is A4 and the version I submitted was intended for A2, I had to check if the current version was acceptable as is or not.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Dataviz Poster</title>
      <link>https://linetonthat.github.io/post/a-dataviz-poster/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 11:59:37 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://linetonthat.github.io/post/a-dataviz-poster/</guid>
      <description>Designed to be printed When I design personal data visualizations, I usually imagine them printed on paper, although they mostly remain in their digital format. However, there are a few that I would like to see materialized. For example, I printed my sister&amp;rsquo;s vegetable garden data visualization for her. In a way, it&amp;rsquo;s a reminder of what she accomplished in the first year of her vegetable garden. It was easy to do, as it&amp;rsquo;s A4 size (the visualization was done with PowerPoint).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
